You had this kid followed?
Are you trying to pick a fight
with the Ferells?
What are you talking about?
Can you just stop using my daughter
so you won't feel guilty about what happened?
Celestina is alive!
I can feel it in my heart.
And if you refuse to believe that,
let me look for her.
Don't force me to believe
that Celestina is still alive,
because she's already dead.
She and Alyanna are already dead,
and that's what I can feel!
Stop chasing ghosts.
Stop chasing the past
before you get hurt or hurt someone else.
Can I ask a favor from you?
Anything.
Would it be okay
if you oversee some things during the ball?
I can only handle the preparations.
You're not coming?
I'm just a scholar here in GU.
I can't afford that 50,000 pesos.
Florence, oh, come on.
You'll be there.
And I'm sure
Nero will ask you to be his date.
He'll pay for you.
For you.
I'm happy that you invited me, Sir.
Your sizeable contribution
to our beloved university
will certainly be a big help.
Which brings me to my point.
I'm interested in one of your scholars.
Scholars?
Yes.
Her name is Florence Dela Cruz.
And if possible,
I would like to know everything about her.
Words, if it comes from the heart,
can be comforting.
But in our case right now, it won't work.
Because it's more effective
if you cry out all your pain.
Take out all the pain
you're feeling right now.
To be fair, you were able to say words
that made me feel better.
Mama!
Who's there? Is the white van there?
Lord, please no,
I still have a lot of dreams.
Grandfather Garp, what's this for?
This is your chance to tell the truth,
or else...
You know we know
where you feel ticklish the most.
- Here, I know you'll get tickled by this.
- Okay, I'll tell the truth!
What really happened?
Grandfather, I'm not a gossip-monger but...
it all started that day...
Florence needed help.
She's my girlfriend.
Supposedly, to save Florence
from the mean girls who are bullying her.
But, Nero has a different agenda.
Florence, hi.
Hi, Antonia.
Nero. Congratulations to you both.
You guys make such a cute couple.
Thank you.
What happened?
I don't know the details, Grandfather.
I can just imagine
that the pretense slowly became true.
And at the very least,
it was true for Florence.
Really?
Did they spend one night
in each other's arms...
under the rain?
I just imagined that, Grandfather.
You're something else.
How would I know what the real scene was?
Do I watch them 24/7?
Your imagination is okay, bro...
Just like the movies.
Yes, it's like a rated SPG movie.
Well, what I know is...
the make-believe ended up
with them having real feelings,
especially for Florence.
That's when things get complicated,
because the truth is...
Nero is just using Florence
to get to Antonia.
For you.
Thank you.
You're so sweet. Thank you.
Did you like it?
Yes, thank you.
Ouch, it hurts.
That's painful.
So painful.
So imagine what Florence is feeling...
based on her disposition and her cooking.
Good luck with our food
for the next few weeks.
Or worse... months!
Ms. Serafica?
Grandfather Garp?
Hey!
I already told you the truth!
Nero?
Don Ferell, Nero is not here.
My goodness, where did that kid go?
Don Ferell...
Don Ferell, I saw Nero.
Do you remember the first time we met?
And you mistook me for someone else.
You thought I was the one
being set up with you.
But what I didn't understand is,
why do you assume that I would agree
to go on a blind date with you?
I was just thinking
if my grandfather would set me up,
it would be with someone worth my time.
Am I?
Am I worth your time?
I will always treasure the time
that I spent with you.
How about her?
Is she worth your time?
What I know is,
I'm happy when I'm with her.
Did you tell her about your true feelings?
What are you waiting for?
I'm scared.
You're right to be afraid.
Florence is ambitious,
and you are her way out of poverty.
Basically, her entry ticket to our world.
Do you think that she loves you?
Florence is not that kind of person.
All right.
Let's say, you're correct.
Do you think that she loves you?
What if she hurts you?
Do you think you can still recover?
I'm the only one who truly loves you, Nero.
I'm the only one who can understand you.
I will always protect you
and I'll never break your heart.
What are you talking about?
Break up with her.
Finish whatever it is you have,
and let's get back together.
Do you think I still want
to reconcile with you?
Do you think you have a choice, Nero?
I can destroy her.
She lied in front of the school
when she agreed to be your girlfriend.
And I can make a case to the dean
that it's a violation of
the ethical standards of our school.
And the least that could happen is...
it could warrant a suspension.
And if I'm not mistaken,
that suspension could cancel her scholarship.
Grandfather Garp won't allow that.
The Ferell Family
isn't the only influential one.
My family is pretty capable too.
But if you hurt his only daughter,
maybe he'll start looking
in a different direction.
Maybe even towards the direction
of the Almeros.
If you don't get back with me,
I will make sure
that Florence will not just
be kicked out of university.
But also, none of her dreams and ambitions
will come true.
And I'll make sure that she'll end up
in the slums where she came from,
and she can be selling lunches
in plastic containers
at construction sites.
I did my research on her.
Do you know the condition of her father?
Florence is an easy target.
And I can hurt her in ways
that you can't even imagine.
She's my girlfriend.
Shall we, my Chummy pie?
Take a look, is it beautiful?
It's really beautiful.
You're right...
it's so beautiful.
Okay, you can use the other side.
Nero!
I've been calling and calling.
You had us all worried.
I'm sorry, Grandfather.
Go ahead and rest.
It's okay.
- I just want to...
- Hey, stop.
I know what you're going to say.
And... what I can only say is,
we don't have to talk about that anymore.
Our agreement was clear.
So...
I have no right to feel bad.
I should be happy, right?
Because it seems like you and Antonia
are now okay.
It's mission accomplished.
We succeeded in making her jealous.
Yes.
It's good that you understand.
But still... thanks for your help.
I am now happy knowing you'll be able
to achieve your dreams for yourself...
and your family.
You didn't assume, right?
No.
Good.
I really wish you
all the happiness you deserve.
Good luck, Florence.
I am now happy knowing you'll be able
to achieve your dreams for yourself...
and your family.
"I am now happy knowing you'll be able
to achieve your dreams
for yourself and your family"?
What?
What did he mean by that?
I won't be able to achieve my dreams before?
Hey!
So, are you okay now?
What kind of question is that?
Of course not.
Florence is not defined by men.
I'm sure she's okay now.
Why did you bother to ask me
if you have your own opinions
whether I'm okay or not?
So, what's the answer?
I'm okay but I'm somehow...
still annoyed with what happened,
but what can I do
when I'm just a simple Dela Cruz, right?
And I went to GU to study
and achieve my dreams.
So...
what's your plan?
Plan on what?
On how to invade a country?
Of course, what are your plans for the ball?
Nothing.
What do you mean by nothing?
Nothing. As in, nothing.
- Nothing?
- I already told you.
I don't have 50,000 pesos
for that per-plate meal.
And since I don't have a date anymore,
and I don't have money for that,
do I really have to fight for that ball?
You know what?
Sometimes I hate poor people.
You act like you don't have
rich kid friends in us.
That's right.
Plus, the best revenge is to be beautiful.
And the best place to be beautiful
is at the Grand Gyronella University Ball.
Exactly.
Except for the judgment of poor people,
I agree with Camille and Aira.
We can contribute to cover for you.
That will go to a good cause, right?
And we're excited about a makeover.
Yes!
Makeover?
Yes.
- Me?
- Yes.
Makeover.
I don't want to.
Don't experiment on me.
But you're our friend, Florence.
Friends help each other.
Friends are always there for each other.
And friends party together!
Friends always offer a helping hand.
And when you get murdered,
we, your friends, will avenge your death.
True.
You're overreacting with the murder part.
So, game?
No.
Look.
Yes... I think we found it.
Perfection.
I agree.
[Follow The Flowers]
What's this?
Follow the flowers?
There are flowers and candles.
[Watch Your Step]
[Will You Be My Date?]
I'm just making you laugh.
But it doesn't change the fact
that my scrambled eggs are delicious.
Tomorrow, I'll have sunny side up.
So, you like eggs.
Take it easy, you might turn into a chicken.
Good one.
So just cry it all out.
Take out all the pain
you're feeling right now.
To be fair...
you said words that made me feel better now.
Florence...
What happened?
So... will you be my date?
Don't you have any other choice?
Ma'am Serafica?
Am I late already?
I will cook right away.
No, you will not cook today.
I will take care of the house.
You focus on the ball.
I believe this is
a very important day, right?
No, Ma'am Serafica.
- That will be easy and...
- I don't think so.
Because someone informed me
that you'll be needing at least one whole day
to prepare.
- What?
- Yes.
Who said that?
Ma'am Serafica, what is going on?
And who said that I have to
prepare the whole day?
Them?
What are you doing here?
Girl, we weren't informed
that you're staying here in the mansion.
I heard you're a scholar of Don Ferell,
but to actually live here?
So, is it always a fun time
with the Ferell boys?
Will you stop it?
I'm a cook here.
So what do you cook for the Ferells?
And as the saying goes,
have you made your way to their hearts?
Will you tell me why you're here?
Or I'll throw you out.
Hey, you easily get mad.
Well, we brought you your glam team.
Glam team?
Why?
Do you think
you're going to the ball unprepared?
What?
There they are.
What do you mean?
This is it, guys.
Welcome to this year's Grand Gyronella Ball.
A celebration of humanity and beauty.
And in a world full of people who are angry
and want to hurt others...
this year's theme will be
"Return to Kindness".
We are here live at Levante Continental
for the Grand Gyronella ball.
But this year,
there's a difference in our celebration
because it's not just glitz and glamour.
This is also a celebration of humanity.
In fact, for the very first time...
Oh, look at who we have here.
Linalyn Ysabel Tibayan Hidalgo,
more commonly known as Lina,
she literally is the luckiest girl
on the campus
because she is literally lucky
coming from a family who won the lottery.
What I can only say is...
I hope it's for everyone.
She looks so beautiful.
A lot of the students here in Gyronella
look like they're wearing gowns
from different designers,
may it be from the Philippines
or all over the world.
I cannot wait to see
what everyone else is wearing.
Oh, who would have thought
these two will recover
from the debacle that is Agora day.
We have Camille Villarico Cortez
and Aira Samson Rivera,
the famous "Take it-Take it"
of the Gyronella University.
Because if you take the other,
you automatically get the other one.
It's so beautiful here at the Grand GU Ball
and I love our theme for this year.
It's super groundbreaking
because this year's theme
is all about serving people,
those who can't reach,
like, the ones in our university.
Oh my goodness!
Looks like the Ferell Brothers
won't be arriving in five today.
Well, it's about time they stop
acting like a boy band group.
In fact, I have a very interesting trivia
about the Ferell brothers.
Because the term Ferell Brothers
is actually a misnomer
because they are not brothers,
but first cousins.
And I think this is a testament
to how well Don Ferell raised them
because even if they are not brothers,
they grew up in a tight-knit family
despite being insanely wealthy.
Oh, and speaking of Don Ferell,
it truly is an honor
to be graced by his presence.
Because if there's a person
who is referred to in the saying,
"need no further introduction",
it's probably him.
Because what else can I say about him
that hasn't been said yet
in his numerous features
and various business magazines?
Thank you so much for attending tonight,
Don Ferell.
All of the people here in Gyronella
are actually so excited for this year's theme
because it's groundbreaking.
I mean, we're so used
to just glitz and glamour, and partying...
Oh, this is a surprise.
So surprising
that I didn't prepare an introduction
for him.
But who needs cue cards or whatnot,
if you're Don Rogelio Almero
of the Almero Group of Companies?
So, the rumors must be true then,
that the Almeros have taken an interest
in our beloved university.
The Dean must be really excited,
because the entrance of Almeros
to our beloved university
would mean
a very significant financial contribution.
Ma'am Serafica, how is Florence?
We're already late.
Bad news, Owen.
It looks like
Florence doesn't want to go anymore.
She's been locking herself in the room
for quite some time now.
What happened?
And it looks like the king and queen
have arrived.
Here we have
Ms. Antonia Scarlet Vamorida Fuentes,
escorted by none other
than Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell.
Antonia looks perfect in her sparkly,
like-a-night-filled-with-stars dress.
I think that's how I would be describing it.
Girls... where's our chicken?
I don't think there's a chicken
on our menu for tonight, Camille.
Lina.
What she meant was,
where is the person we're rooting for?
Where is Florence?
Exactly.
Oh my gosh.
Where is she?
Florence?
Can we just talk?
No need.
I don't want people to see me, Owen.
I look like a fool.
Come on, Florence, it can't be that bad.
Please, Owen, this is not me.
You'll all laugh at me once you see me.
I just want to see you and who knows,
maybe Ma'am Serafica and I can help you.
Ma'am, here are the keys. I'm sorry.
Please step aside. I will now open the door.
- Okay.
- So we'll find out what's wrong.
Okay, thank you for the update.
What's going on?
Is Florence okay?
It seems she's not happy
with how she turned out earlier,
that's why the stylist said
that she might not come.
What?
It can't be that bad.
I want to get out of here and go to her
to really see what's happening.
She can't do this.
She has to be here.
Florence is here.
What?
Wow!
That is crazy, bro!
I'm not going to lie. They look good.
- Florence is so beautiful.
- Right.
And she looks so rich in what she's wearing.
I agree.
Didn't I tell you?
Everything will be all right.
You look perfect.
Go, Florence.
Raise the flag of people like us
at the poverty level.
Babycakes, just let it be.
Our point is,
to let Florence carry out our dream.
Well...
What's important is
for all of us to be happy and...
Celebrate!
Oh my gosh.
To be fair, girl,
you're one of the contenders.
You're part of the top five here.
Also, she has the best accessory.
What accessory?
What else, but... a Ferell.
Ferell.
I'm just happy to be here
and spend time with you girls.
Really, and you're trying to be cute, Owen.
You're the topnotcher of the Ferells.
Which brings me to my point.
Look at the other Ferells...
It looks like our fundraising for tonight
will be lucrative.
Exactly.
Good thing your friend gave us a side hustle.
Yes, we can have extra funds
for our household budget.
What kind of event is this?
I'm wondering too.
This is the Gyronella University event.
Yes, you're right.
Maybe your daughter is there.
No, I don't think so.
They said it's 50,000 pesos per plate here.
Where are we going to get the money
to pay for that?
- Let's call her.
- Okay, go ahead and call her.
Let me fish out my phone.
Hello.
Florence?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
This is Serafica.
Florence left her cellphone behind.
Where is she?
She didn't tell you?
What?
The reason why she's not here
is that she's attending the Grand GU Ball.
But don't worry because once you see her,
I'm sure you'll both be
very proud of her, okay?
Bye.
Come on.
Babycakes?
Isn't that just a code?
Hey, Buttercup, you got jealous right away.
Maybe that's someone else.
What do you mean it's someone else?
Enough, my goodness gracious.
- Stop it.
- I'm the only one you love?
Of course, my Babycup.
I love it when I do this.
I just love it.
I'm the only one she loves.
Of course.
- Really. Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Salute!
Don Ferell, I don't think I need
to introduce you to Don Rogelio.
Please call me Rogelio, Dean.
I just want to say, Mr. Rogelio,
that we thank you with all our hearts
for your donation.
And with the support of the Ferells,
our university can expand
the scholarship program
so we can accommodate
more students who are not as fortunate,
but deserving of the quality of education
the school gives.
Thank you, Rogelio.
Thank you for your generosity.
You're welcome, Garpidio.
It's about time that we work together
to create a positive impact
on the lives of the majority.
I agree.
She looks like someone familiar, right?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I think it's the eyes.
That's what I also noticed
the first time I saw her.
It kind of looks like Alyanna.
Are you suggesting
that she's the missing daughter of Alyanna?
The biggest party on this side of the world
is about to start.
Are you ready
for the super spreader event of the season?
Because we will be spreading
both fun and goodwill at the same time.
So, what are you waiting for?
Return to party,
Return to Kindness starts now.
Fundraising?
Well, Florence, since you left me in charge,
we thought of different activities
to raise funds for the poor.
Trust me, Florence,
even I was impressed with
the idea of Camille and Aira.
Yes.
I'm excited about whatever activity is that.
Powerful.
Let's go.
Hey, now you know.
You learned how to do it, Lina.
Stop that.
Stop looking at her.
At least now you know
what type of a woman Florence is.
Or maybe you should continue looking at her.
Imagine, she's now with Owen.
She easily moved on from you.
And that just raises my suspicion of her.
She was just using you to level up her life.
And because you're no longer an option,
she quickly looked for an alternative.
She soon looked for someone else.
Excuse me.
One more, please.
So now, may we call on for the next item,
Ms. Florence Dela Cruz?
For this item, Florence will be
cooking you a private dinner
and a set-up by the beach.
So, Ms. Florence?
Let's get this bidding started.
Private dinner cooked by Ms. Florence.
Anyone?
One million pesos.
It's you who said that Florence is our cook,
and it's not good to see
that both Ferells are fighting because of her.
Sit together and talk.
Man-to-man.
A Ferell to a Ferell.
I don't care what others will say.
My God, dude, you're both Ferells.
Have you forgotten what Grandpa said?
That if Ferells have a problem,
we fix it together.
That's right. You better fix your problem.
The last thing we want
is to tear each other apart
because of Florence.
Florence, what happened?
Is there a problem?